infinityward.com 2013-09-29

# ACTIVISION

This online property uses "cookies". Cookies enable users to navigate around online properties, such as websites, and also enable us to tailor content, marketing, and improve user experience. For further details on cookies, including how to disable them, please see the Cookies section of this Privacy Policy. Please note that without cookies enabled we cannot guarantee that this online property and your experience whilst visiting it will work as intended. By using this online property you agree, and we will assume you consent, to receive cookies unless you manage your cookies opt out choices as set out in the Cookies section of this Privacy Policy. 

Below you will find the Activision Privacy Policy. This Privacy Policy was last updated on August 20, 2013. 

Your privacy is our policy. 

##  **SUMMARY**

_By using this Activision website, mobile or tablet app, or other online property, you confirm you have read and agree to the Privacy Policy set out below, including Activision undertaking the following activities:_

  * _Collecting, processing and using demographic information about me such as my age, gender, interests and the IP address I use, to combine it with my personal information and to use it for analytic and marketing purposes;_
  * _Contacting me from time to time by email to ask for my opinion and inviting me to online polls or surveys, linking the information I provide to my personal information and using this information for marketing purposes;_
  * _Using web beacons (or clear GIFs) on their Web site or in e-mail messages or placing own and third party cookies on my computer or device or using flash technology where appropriate to tailor the service to my interests and to select ads and products that are more relevant to me;_
  * _Disclosing my personal information to Activision owned subsidiaries and wholly owned group companies;_
  * _Collecting, processing and storing the personal information I provide on servers in the United States or other countries where Activision or its affiliates, subsidiaries, agents or vendors maintain facilities or business operations; in some countries, the data protection level may be lower than in the European Union, but Activision will take reasonable measures to safeguard my privacy rights under applicable data protection laws._

##  **ACTIVISION ONLINE PRIVACY POLICY**

As one of the world's largest providers of interactive entertainment software, Activision is committed to providing the best on-line entertainment in a secure on-line environment. 

Activision Publishing, Inc. (including its wholly owned subsidiaries) ("Activision") respects the privacy rights of our online visitors., We have adopted this Privacy Policy to explain how we collect, store, and use the information you provide to us online. 

By using this website, application for mobile phone or tablet, or other online product or service provided to you by Activision (collectively “website and/or other online property/properties”), you signify your assent to the Activision Privacy Policy. If you do not agree to this Privacy Policy, please do not use this website or other online property. We reserve the right to make changes to this Privacy Policy, and please check back from time to time to ensure you are aware of any changes. If we make a material change to this Privacy Policy, we will post a notice of the change on www.activision.com and also on this Privacy Policy. Your continued use of our website or other online property will signify your acceptance of these changes. If you do not agree to any of these changes, please do not continue using this website or other online property. This Privacy Policy shall form part of the terms governing your use of this website or other online property. 

This Privacy Policy and the certification seal located to your right confirms that Activision is a valid licensee and participating member in the Entertainment Software Rating Board's (“ESRB”) Privacy Online Program: ESRB Privacy Online. To protect your privacy, we have voluntarily undertaken this privacy initiative and Activision has been reviewed and certified by ESRB Privacy Online to meet established online information collection and use practices. As part of this privacy program, we are subject to frequent audits of our site and other enforcement and accountability mechanisms administered independently by ESRB. 

Whenever you visit a web site that displays the ESRB Privacy Online certification seal, you can expect to be notified of: 

* Whether a company uses cookies, tracks IP Addresses or uses other passive means to collect information;  
* Who, if anyone, is collecting your personal information and how will it be used;  
* With whom, if anyone, will your personal information be shared;  
* What choices you have with regard to the use of your personal information;  
* How you can access and, if necessary, change the personal information a company collects and maintains;  
* Whether and how information is collected from children under 13;  
* How a company ensures data security, quality, and integrity; and,  
* Where and how to ask questions or file complaints. 

This Privacy Policy currently applies to websites and other online properties operated by Activision that post or link to this Privacy Policy, which includes, without limitation, the following: 

Skylanders Cloud Patrol (available as an app for selected mobile phone and tablet operating systems) 

In addition, Activision also owns several other websites and other online properties not listed above, and we may from time to time add new websites and other online properties that may or may not be listed above. Please note, however, that this Privacy Policy applies only to Activision websites and other online properties posting or linking to this Privacy Policy, but not to websites or other online properties maintained by other companies or organizations to which we link and Activision cannot and does not guarantee the security of any personal information disclosed on those third party sites. In addition, please note that we may solicit third parties to collect personal information on our behalf and in such cases such third parties will be instructed to comply with this Privacy Policy and applicable data protection law. Finally, please note that this Privacy Policy applies only to the collection, use and disclosure of information obtained online and not to the collection of information obtained offline. Any collection of information obtained offline will also be in compliance with applicable data protection law. 

Activision is a licensee of the ESRB's Privacy Online Program. If you believe that we have not responded to your inquiry or your inquiry has not been satisfactorily addressed, please contact ESRB at 

ESRB  
Attn.:Privacy Online Program  
317 Madison Avenue , 22nd Floor  
New York , NY 10017  

##    
**What information does Activision collect**? 

Activision only collects personal information from you on a voluntary basis. When you submit personal information to Activision, it will usually take the form of: (1) Web site registration; (2) contests and promotions; (3) customer service; (4) demo downloads; (5) purchase of a product or service through our online stores; (6) use of a website or other online property (including Online Services (as defined below)); (7) online submission of your résumé for job openings. The information we collect may include personal information such as your name, e-mail address, phone number, and home address. In addition, we may collect demographic information such as your age, gender and interests. We may also obtain information about you from other sources, as far as such other sources are legally entitled to share such information, and combine that information with information we have collected from you. 

##  *** Web Site Registration**

Activision may collect personal information from you when registering as a website or other online property member, including your name, address, e-mail address, and phone number. We may also collect demographic information such as your gender and birth date, which we may combine with your personal information and use it for marketing purposes. Once this information is combined it is all considered personal information. Information collected from those who register on our websites or other online properties is used to provide registrants the benefits associated with such registration (e.g., subscription to newsletters; access to the latest game news and contests; message boards, chat rooms or forums; and product registration.). From time to time, we may contact you to ask you for your opinion about certain matters in the form of online polls or surveys, including your opinion with respect to our games or other products and services. Your responses to these polls help us provide products and services of interest to you. 

##  *** Contests and Promotions**

From time to time, Activision may run contests or promotions on our websites and other online properties and collect certain personal information in connection with such event. The information may include your name, address, e-mail address, phone number, and birth date. This information will be used only for the purpose of your participation in product-specific contests and promotions as well as informing you of upcoming products and services. 

##  *** Customer Service**

In order to provide you with the best possible customer service, Activision may collect some personal information from you including your name, e-mail address and birth date. This information will be used only for the purpose of solving your customer support inquiry and will be saved for twelve (12) months in the event additional customer support requests arise. 

##  *** Demo Downloads/Mature-Rated Content**

Visitors interested in accessing Mature-rated content or downloading demonstration versions of Activision games with an ESRB rating of "M" (Mature) or PEGI 18 may need to provide a valid credit card number and expiration date. Such information will be used only for the purpose of verifying age and will not be stored. 

##  *** Résumés**

Activision allows for the online submission of résumés. Personal information collected in association with résumés will be used solely for the purpose of accepting and evaluating candidate submissions for job postings. This information may only be shared within the Activision group if you have given your prior consent or if the respective job relates to another company within the Activision group. Information collected in association with résumés is not subject to the terms of this Online Privacy Statement. 

##  ***Online Services**

Activision may provide you with a variety of online services such as accounts, and online games (“Online Services”). Activision may collect non-personal information from you, such as scores, rankings, game play statistics, game feature usages, and achievements. We may also collect information stored in your account preferences and online profiles, including, for example, your purchases and friends lists. Activision may combine non-personal information with personal information in order to tailor advertisements, web pages, game play experiences, products, virtual goods and Online Services for you. 

Further, use of certain features of Online Services, such as messages boards, profiles, and contributing user generated content, may involve disclosure of personal information about you by you. You acknowledge that you have no right or expectation of privacy or confidentiality when using such features of Online Services. 

In some instances, we may use a third party gaming service to provide authentication for Online Services, and in such case you may be asked to provide your account information associated with that third party service when signing up for Online Services. In addition, if registering for Online Services directly from a third-party gaming service, certain membership information there will be transferred automatically to Activision when you register. 

##  *** Purchase of goods or services through our online store**

Visitors purchasing goods and services through one of our affiliate online stores will need to provide a valid credit card number and expiration date, in addition to name, e-mail address, phone number, and home address.Whatever the activity may be, we will only collect information to the extent deemed reasonably necessary to fulfill your requests and legitimate business objectives as permitted under applicable data protection legislation. 

Activision may, from time to time, offer you the ability to send an e-mail to friends or family by using our "send-a-friend" tool.  Any information entered for "send-a-friend" messages are used only to send the requested message; we delete both sender and recipient e-mail addresses after sending the message. In using our “send-a-friend” tool you confirm that you and party to whom you are sending the message know each other. 

##  **What happens if I refuse to provide my personal information?**

If you do not want to submit personal information that is necessary to provide the service or to fulfill your request, you will not be able to access and/or participate in certain activities. For example, you will not be able to register on Activision.com or participate in certain contests and promotions or access and/or use other online features or Online Services. In addition, your refusal to submit personal information may limit our ability to respond to your customer support inquiry in a timely fashion. 

##  **What are “Cookies” and does Activision use cookies, track IP Addresses, or use other passive means to collect information?**

Activision uses cookies on its websites and other online properties. A "cookie" is a small bit of record-keeping information that many websites and other online properties often store on a user's computer or device in order to anonymously identify it and associate activity with it. Cookies typically do not include people's names, or e-mail addresses. 

When visiting our websites and other online services you can choose whether or not to let us enable cookies. We use cookies to optimize your visit, make your browsing experience as effective as possible, and let you know about offers that we think will interest you. This means that if you refuse, your use of our websites and other online properties may be impaired as a result. 

Depending on the Activision website or other online property you are using, and the country you are based in, cookies may be set on your computer or device by either: 

Activision - to recognize and associate activity with your computer or device when it visits an Activision website or other online property. Activision cookies cannot be used to recognize or associate activity with your computer or device when it visits other, third party websites or online properties. 

Third Parties – to enable third party features or functionality to be provided on or through Activision's websites or other online properties (e.g. advertising and analytics). The third parties that set these cookies can recognize your computer or device both when it visits Activision websites or other online properties in question and also when it visits certain other non-Activision websites or online properties that use the third party's features and functionality 

##  **Types Of Cookies**

  * _Strictly Necessary Cookies_

These cookies are essential in order to enable you to move around websites or online properties and use their features, such as accessing secure areas of a website. Without these cookies, services you have asked for, like secure login areas, cannot be provided. 

  * _Performance (or Analytics) Cookies_

These cookies collect information about how visitors use a website or online property, for instance which pages visitors go to most often, and if they get error messages from web pages. These cookies don’t collect information that identifies a visitor. All information these cookies collect is aggregated and therefore anonymous. They are only used to improve how a website or other online property works. We generally contract with independent research and measurement companies, such as Google Analytics, to provide these services on our behalf and which may also be subject to their own privacy policies. 

  * _Functionality Cookies_

These cookies allow the website or online property to remember choices you make (such as your user name, language or the region you are in) and provide enhanced, more personal features. These cookies can also be used to remember changes you have made to text size, fonts and other parts of web pages that you can customize. They may also be used to provide services you have asked for such as watching a video. The information these cookies collect may be anonymized and they cannot track your browsing activity on other websites. 

  * _Advertising Cookies_

    * These cookies are used to deliver adverts more relevant to you and your interests. They are also used to limit the number of times you see an advertisement as well as help measure the effectiveness of the advertising campaign. They are usually placed by advertising networks with the website or online property operator’s permission. They remember that you have visited a website and this information is shared with other organizations such as advertisers. Quite often advertising cookies will be linked to site functionality provided by the other organization. In certain countries our websites may partner with third party online advertising and analytics companies to tailor and deliver advertisements, products, services, and promotions on our websites and other online properties, as well as advertisements, products, services, and promotions on websites and other online properties which we do not control. To help select the ads of greatest interest to you, these companies may use cookies, Flash technology, and similar technologies to collect and track non-personal information such as demographic information (e.g., gender, occupation, etc.), aggregated information, search keywords, geo-location and online data (for example, clickstream data such as browser type, language, IP address, time/date) to select advertisements that are more relevant to your interests, to better personalize the experience for you and tailor advertisements. In some instances, we may allow third-party companies to collect certain anonymous information when you visit our website. These companies may use non-personally identifiable information during your visits to this and other websites in order to provide third party advertisements about goods and services likely to be of greater interest to you. These companies typically use a cookie or a third party web beacon to collect this information.

    * To learn more about Advertising Cookies visit the Network Advertising Initiative (NAI) at [http://networkadvertising.org](http://networkadvertising.org/) or [http://youronlinechoices.com](http://youronlinechoices.com/)

##  **Managing Cookies**

You can review your options to manage cookies by: 

  * by clicking on the opt out links provided in Appendix 1 at the end of this Privacy Policy 

  * by opening the “Help” menu on the browser menu bar. Most browsers will tell you how you can disable or delete cookies or set your browser to alert you when cookies are being sent to your computer. 

  * visiting <http://networkadvertising.org/managing/opt_out.asp> and/or [http://youronlinechoices.com](http://youronlinechoices.com/) for choices to opt out of advertising 

If you reject all cookies, you may not be able to use certain features of our websites and other online properties (including sign in). 

##  **Permission to Use Cookies**

By using our websites and other online properties you agree, and we will assume you consent, to receive cookies through our websites and online properties unless you manage your cookie choices by one of the means set out above. 

If a cookies choice setting is not available through either the third party provider listed in Appendix 1, your browser, or at <http://networkadvertising.org/managing/opt_out.asp> or [http://youronlinechoices.com](http://youronlinechoices.com/) then by using the applicable Activision website or other online property you agree, and we will assume you consent, to receive cookies through that Activision website or other online property. Please also note that the use of information obtained by third party providers listed in Appendix 1 through cookies placed by them is also subject to their own privacy policies. 

If you have a registration account with us, information collected by cookies may be associated with your registration account. 

##  **Flash cookies and web beacons**

Adobe Flash Player is an application that allows sites to deploy dynamic web content. Adobe Flash and similar applications use technology to remember settings, preferences, and usage in ways that are similar to browser cookies, but are managed through a different interface than your web browser. You can access your Flash management tools from http://www.adobe.com/ directly to manage your cookie settings. 

From time to time, we may use web beacons (or clear GIFs) on our websites or other online properties or include them in the e-mail messages we send you. Web beacons (also known as "web bugs") are small strings of code that provide a method of delivering a graphic image on a web page or in an email message for the purpose of transferring data. We use web beacons for many purposes, including site traffic reporting, unique visitor counts, advertising and email auditing and reporting, and personalization. 

We also keep track of Internet Protocol (IP) addresses. An IP address is a number that is used by computers on the network to identify your computer every time you log on to the Internet. 

Activision may use and share non-personally identifiable (e.g., anonymized or aggregated) information obtained from cookies with third parties such as service providers or advertising partners. An example of the use of such information would be an anonymous group that we assign to an interest categories or segment such as region, gaming preferences, or a combination. We may also share non-personally identifiable information obtained from cookies with third parties such as service providers or advertising networks in order to permit them to provide services on our behalf or to partner with us in selecting and serving advertisements for us or our advertising partners. 

##  **Social Network Sites**

If you have signed in to a social networking site, such as Facebook, it may have set a cookie on your device which recognizes you when you view content on our websites and other online properties. These cookies allow you to share content across social media via the use of sharing settings.  See your social networking site’s Terms of Use and Privacy Policy for details. For additional details, please see the Social Media Note below. 

##  **More Information**

If you would like to find out more about cookies you may find the following link useful: 

<http://www.allaboutcookies.org/>

##  **Who is collecting my personal information and how will it be used?**

The information you submit to our websites and other online properties is collected and used by Activision Publishing, Inc., 3100 Ocean Park Boulevard, Santa Monica, CA 90405, USA. European Union 

If you are visitor to our websites or other online properties from a member state of the European Union, then the information you submit is collected and used by Activision Blizzard UK Limited of 3 Roundwood Avenue, Stockley Park, Uxbridge, UB11 1AF, England. Activison Blizzard UK Limited is registered as data controller with the UK Information Commissioner’s Office with registration number Z1095341. If you have any questions about how Activision Blizzard UK Limited uses and protects your personal information you can contact us in writing at the above address (Attention: Legal & Business Affairs/Privacy Policy) or call us on 00 44 203 060 1000.  

Activision may disclose personal information to vendors or employ vendors to collect personal information on Activision's behalf. These vendors provide internal support to our websites and other online properties by operating some of the services we provide you (“vendors”). When requesting these services, you may be asked to supply your name, address, e-mail address, and/or other personal information. Activision does not allow vendors to share such information with any other party unless reasonably necessary to provide the service or use such information for any other purposes, and requires them to adhere to Activision's Privacy Policy and where applicable data processing agreements concluded between Activision and such vendors. 

In addition, if you are a visitor to our websites and other online properties from outside the U.S., the personal information you provide may be collected, processed and stored directly on servers in the United States or other countries where Activision or our affiliates, subsidiaries, agents or vendors maintain facilities or business operations; collected, processed and stored on servers in other countries and then transferred to servers in the United States or other countries where Activision or our affiliates, subsidiaries, agents or vendors maintain facilities or business operations.  If you do not agree to the collection, processing, storage and transfer of your information, please do not provide your information when requested and stop using our websites and other online properties. 

##    
**With whom does Activision share my personal information?**

Activision does not share or sell your personal information with outside third parties for those third parties to use for their own purposes without your agreement. Activision discloses personal information only in accordance with this Privacy Policy with: 

  * Vendors as set out above 

  * Other third parties as necessary to complete any transaction through our websites or other online properties and/or provide Online Services you have requested. Notwithstanding, you agree we may disclose personal information in the good faith belief that we are required to do so by law, including but not limited to disclosure to law enforcement or other government officials in connection with an investigation of fraud, intellectual property infringements, or other activity that is illegal or may expose you or us to legal liability. We may review your gameplay and other account information in order to investigate allegations of cheating, hacking or any other breach or alleged breach of any applicable Terms of Use or this Privacy Policy and disclose your personal information to our legal advisors, consultants and law enforcement or other government officials. In addition, in the event of a merger, acquisition, reorganization, bankruptcy, or other similar event, Activision's customer information including personal information may be transferred to our successor or assign. 

Please note that any information, including personally identifiable information that you reveal in a bulletin board, message board, chat room or other public forum is publicly viewable. 

##  **Can I choose how my personal information is used?**

If you want to remove yourself from individual contests or promotions, or from receiving e-mail newsletters from Activision, simply click the unsubscribe link in the email newsletter or access your account from [_http://www.activision.com/_](http://www.activision.com/) and edit/delete your information. You will need your password to access your personal account. If you do not want Activision to reply to your customer support inquiry, you may opt-out from receiving a response by contacting us by regular mail at: Activision Publishing, Inc., 3100 Ocean Park Boulevard, Santa Monica, CA 90405 USA, ATTN: Business and Legal Affairs/Privacy Policy. We will be happy to honor your request. However, notwithstanding any removals under this paragraph, you acknowledge and agree there may be certain instances where we may elect to notify you about your account itself, such as to inform you that your account may be expiring or provide you with other relevant information about your account. 

##  ***Your California Privacy Rights**

Since 2005, California Civil Code Section 1798.83 permits our customers who are California residents to request certain information regarding our disclosure of personal information to third parties for their direct marketing purposes.  We do not share our customer's personal information with unaffiliated third parties for their own direct marketing purposes.  For inquiries regarding our disclosure policy, please send us an e-mail to [_websitedisclosurepolicy@activision.com_](mailto:websitedisclosurepolicy@activision.com), or write us at : Activision Publishing, Inc., 3100 Ocean Park Boulevard, Santa Monica, CA 90405 USA, ATTN: Business and Legal Affairs/Privacy Policy. We will be happy to honor your request. 

##    ***Social Media Note**

You also can engage with our content on or through third-party social networking sites, such as Facebook and Twitter (or third-party social media plug-ins and applications) ("Social Media"). When you engage with our content on or through Social Media, you may allow us to have access to certain information from your Social Media profile (e.g., name, e-mail address, photo, gender, birthday, location, your list of friends, people you follow and/or who follow you, the posts or the ‘likes’ you make) to deliver the content or as part of the operation of the application. We may also obtain other information from your interaction with our content (e.g., content viewed, game performance, high scores, and information about advertisements within the content you have been shown or may have clicked on). 

When you provide information from your Social Media account, it can help enable us to do things like (1) give you exclusive content, (2) personalize your online experience with us within and outside our websites (and/or applications), and (3) contact you in accordance with your marketing preferences through the social networking sites or directly by sending you the latest news, special offerings, and rewards. By doing so, you consent to the use of this information in accordance with our Privacy Policy. When you post personal information publicly through our websites or other online properties, or on social networking sites, it may be publicly viewed by other members of these sites and we cannot prevent further use of the information by third parties. 

Social Media sites and applications will often allow you to control what data you share by changing your privacy settings with that Social Meda site or application. For more information about how your Social Media sites and applications use and protect your personal information, please refer to their privacy policies and terms of use. 

##  ***Mobile Application Partners**

We partner with certain mobile analytics, advertising, and technology partners, which may include, but not be limited to SWRVE New Media , Flurry, Kochava and others. Such mobile partners may use a tracking pixel, agent or any other visitor identification technology that collects, uses, shares and stores data about end users and digital ad campaigns promoting our mobile apps, and by choosing to use Activision mobile apps you hereby consent to such activities. Please see Appendix 1 of this Activision Privacy Policy for details of those partners privacy policies and opt out options. 

##  ***How do I access my personal information?**

If for any reason you wish to view, correct or delete the personal information collected about you simply access your account from the Web site or [_http://www.activision.com/_](http://www.activision.com/) and edit/delete your information as necessary. You will need your password to access your personal account. You may also send us an email asking us to delete your account at removeaccount@activision.com. In the alternative, you may write to us at Activision Publishing, Inc., 3100 Ocean Park Boulevard, Santa Monica, CA 90405 USA, ATTN: Business and Legal Affairs/Privacy Policy (Activision Blizzard UK Limited, 3 Roundwood Avenue, Stockley Park, Uxbridge, UB11 1AF, UK for users from a member state of the European Union). We will be happy to review, update or remove information as appropriate. Residual copies of information that has been deleted from your account may remain in our backup systems for up to 30 days. In certain cases, we may still retain your information to resolve disputes, enforce our user agreement, or comply with legal requirements; in this case, your personal information will be blocked from use for any other purpose. 

##    
***Does Activision collect personal information from children under 13?**

We do not knowingly collect or store any personally identifiable information such as name, address, or e-mail address from children under 13. 

We recognize a special obligation to protect personal information obtained from young children. We urge parents to instruct their children to never give out their real names, addresses, or phone numbers, without permission, when on-line. Children under the age of 17 and over the age of 12 should encourage their parents to review this Privacy Policy and to contact us if they would like to evoke our opt-out policy or to raise any concerns. 

From time to time, certain portions of our websites and other online properties may allow all users (including children under 13) to disclose a limited amount of personal information without first telling us their age or getting their parent's permission. Such portions of our website operate activities or provide services in a way that does not require prior parental consent. 

##  ***What safeguards does Activision use to protect my personal information?**

Activision takes reasonable steps to ensure data quality such as the accuracy of information obtained from visitors to our websites and other online properties. Activision has also taken reasonable steps to maintain all information collected secure and in its original form, i.e. free from any alteration. Access to all personal information is strictly controlled. In addition, we take reasonable steps to assure that vendors who collect personal information on our behalf provide reasonable levels of protection of personal information. 

##  **How do I ask a question or file a complaint?**

Any questions or complaints about this Privacy Policy can be resolved by addressing written inquires to Activision Publishing, Inc., 3100 Ocean Park Boulevard, Santa Monica, CA 90405, ATTN: Business and Legal Affairs/Privacy Policy, or by calling Business and Legal Affairs/Privacy Policy, ph. (001) 310 255 2000(Activision Blizzard UK Limited, 3 Roundwood Avenue, Stockley Park, Uxbridge, UB11 1AF, UK (ph. 00 44 203 060 1000) for users from a member state of the European Union). 

_**Appendix 1**_

_Your Activision website or online property may contain the following third party Performance (or Analytics) and Advertising cookies. Please follow the links below for details of the Privacy Policies and Opt Out Choices offered by these third parties. Please also see the Cookies section in the Activision Privacy Policy for further options available to manage cookies._

| 

**Online Property**

| 

**Third Party Cookies**

| 

**Third Party Privacy Policies and Opt Out Choices**  
  
---|---|---  
  
**Websites**

| 

Accuen 

| 

<http://accuenmedia.com/optout.htm>  
  
| 

Add This 

| 

<http://www.addthis.com/privacy/privacy-policy>

<http://www.addthis.com/advertising-choices>  
  
| 

Comscore 

| 

<http://www.comscore.com/About_comScore/Privacy_Policy>

<http://www.sitestat.com/>  
  
| 

Cross Pixel Media 

| 

<http://www.networkadvertising.org/choices/>  
  
| 

Data Logix 

| 

<https://www.datalogix.com/privacy/>  
  
| 

Google Analytics 

| 

<https://tools.google.com/dlpage/gaoptout>  
  
| 

MediaMind 

| 

| 

Media6 Degrees 

| 

<http://m6d.com/privacy/privacy-policy/>  
  
| 

ScoreCard Research 

| 

| 

ShareThis 

| 

<http://sharethis.com/privacy>  
  
| 

Tribal Fusion 

| 

| 

Videology 

| 

[_http://www.videologygroup.com/index.php/en/menu-privacy-policy.html_](http://www.videologygroup.com/index.php/en/menu-privacy-policy.html)  
  
**Apps for mobile phones and tablets**

| 

Swrve 

| 

<http://swrve.com/privacy-policy/>  
  
| 

Flurry 

| 

<http://www.flurry.com/user-opt-out.html>  
  
| 

Kochava 

| 

<http://kochava.com/privacy/>
